tutoringhut.com 2013-06-19

# Tutoring Hut - Privacy Policy

> > **PRIVACY POLICY**
>> 
>> ****
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our website and services.**
>> 
>> **This policy will let you know:**
>> 
>>   * **How and when you are consenting to this privacy policy;**
>>   * **TutoringHut.com’s position on the use of its site by minors and the collection of personal information from minors;**
>>   * **What personally identifiable information TutoringHut.com collects from you;**
>>   * **What cookies are and how TutoringHut.com use them;**
>>   * **How TutoringHut.com uses your information and with whom your information is shared;**
>>   * **TutoringHut.com’s policy regarding linked websites;**
>>   * **What your choices are regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information;**
>>   * **What TutoringHut.com’s policy is on allowing you to update, correct, or delete your personally identifiable information;**
>>   * **What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information;**
>>   * **How long your personal data kept;**
>>   * **What we don’t do;**
>>   * **What else you should know about your privacy;**
>>   * **When this policy is effective and how and when changes may be made.**
>> 

>> 
>> **Consent**
>> 
>> **By submitting personal information to us (through the use of this website and/or registering an account) you agree that we may collect, use and disclose such personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and as permitted or required by law. If you do not agree with these terms, do not provide any personal information to us. If you refuse or withdraw your consent, or if you choose not to provide us with any required personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the services of this website and/or advertisements and services that can be offered on our site only if we have access certain personal information.**
>> 
>> **Minors**
>> 
>> **Minors (as defined under the laws of THEIR jurisdiction or residence) may only use this website under the guidance and supervision of their parent(s) or guardian(s) as required by any applicable state or federal law or regulation. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any minor without the implied authorization of their parent or guardian, and we will not use this information if we discover that it has been provided by a minor with such authorization.**
>> 
>> **What personally identifiable information does TutoringHut.com collect from you?**
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com collects information in several ways. Some personal information is gathered when you register for an account. When submitting a request for an account, TutoringHut.com asks for your name, email address, gender, birthday, ethnicity, phone number, education level, and personal interests. Some of information is necessary to contact you regarding your account and is provided voluntarily in order to take advantage of our services. Some of the information that is collected is used to improve our services and offer targeted advertisements.**
>> 
>> **In addition, we may ask you for additional personal information at other times, including, but not limited to, when you enter a sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by Tutoringhut.com and if you report problem with our services. If you contact TutoringHut.com we may keep a record of that correspondence. Whenever TutoringHut.com collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.**
>> 
>> **When we advertise on third party sites**
>> 
>>   
> **When you visit a site on which we advertise and click through our advertisement, we may place cookies on your computer or use  pixel tags. The information that we collect through this technology is not personally identifiable.**
>> 
>> **When you call or write to our Customer Service**
>> 
>>   
> **When you call or write to our Customer Service, we collect contact information, such as name, phone number, mailing address or e-mail address.**
>> 
>> **What are cookies and how does TutoringHut.com use them?**
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A “cookie” is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to:**
>> 
>> **_Estimate our audience size_ \- Each browser accessing TutoringHut.com may be given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage and to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior.**
>> 
>> **_Monitor our services_ – It may be necessary from time to time for TutoringHut.com to monitor and/or track site usage as part of an internal audit of our services and/or the performance of tutors using our site. Portions of this audit may be performed through the use of temporary cookies placed on your computer by the TutoringHut.com site.**
>> 
>> **Third Party Cookies:**
>> 
>> **Some of the advertisements on our website are delivered to you by our web advertising partners. Our advertising partners use cookies to collect information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an advertisement (but not your name, address, or other personal information). This information is used to serve advertisements to you.**
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com also collects IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.**
>> 
>> **How does TutoringHut.com use your information and with whom is your information shared?**
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com’s primary goal in collecting personal information is in providing you the best service possible through its website. The majority of information that is collected about you is for the purpose of verifying account registration and delivering relevant advertisements.**
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com may retain your account information for as long as permitted by law and as long as is necessary to permit you to use our services without the requirement of resubmitting the same information.**
>> 
>> **Except as provided herein, TutoringHut.com shall not sell, rent, trade or otherwise transfer any personal and/or traffic data or communications content to any third party without your explicit permission, unless it is obliged to do so under applicable laws or by order of the competent authorities.**
>> 
>> **In order to provide our services at the lowest possible price to you we may display advertisements. Information collected about you by TutoringHut.com and third party advertisers may be used to deliver more relevant advertisements and content to you.**
>> 
>> **Your information may be used to effect a corporate transaction, in connection with the sale, merger, spin-off or other corporate reorganization of our corporation, where the information is provided to the new controlling entity in regular course of business. In the event of such an occurrence, every effort will be made by TutoringHut.com to inform you of the transfer of your personal information.**
>> 
>> **Your information may be disclosed as is required by our insurers and by regulatory agencies or to employees, contractors, consultants, and agents of TutoringHut.com to perform necessary actions in the normal course of business. No more information than is required in these circumstances will be provided.**
>> 
>> **Linked websites**
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com may contain links that will let you leave TutoringHut.com’s website and access another website. These “linked websites” are not under the control of TutoringHut.com and it is possible that these websites have a different privacy policy. This policy applies solely to personal information that is acquired on this website (TutoringHut.com). TutoringHut.com accepts no responsibility or liability for your use or disclosure of personal information to linked websites.**
>> 
>> **What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?**
>> 
>> **The disclosure of personal information is required to create an account on our site, which is required to access certain services. If you do not wish to disclose the requisite information you are free to discontinue use of the TutoringHut.com website.**
>> 
>> **You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies TutoringHut.com may not be displayed or function in the way intended by Tutoringhut.com.**
>> 
>> **What is TutoringHut.com’s policy on allowing you to update, correct, or delete your personally identifiable information?**
>> 
>> **If you wish to update, correct, or delete any of the information about you stored by TutoringHut.com you can do so by visiting the account settings on your account profile. For all other information changes or requests, please send an inquiry to[info@TutoringHut.com](mailto:info@TutoringHut.com).**
>> 
>> **What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?**
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com shall take the appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect the personal information and IP data provided to it or collected by it necessary to comply fully with any and all applicable laws, obligations, and regulations.**
>> 
>> **Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, TutoringHut.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.**
>> 
>> **How long is your personal information stored?**
>> 
>> **TutoringHut.com will retain your personal information and IP information as long as is permitted by applicable laws and regulations.**
>> 
>> **What we do NOT do?**
>> 
>> **We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, login name, or password, in an unsecure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. Additionally we will not request any confidential or personal information through a social networking site such as Twitter™, MySpace™, or Facebook™.**
>> 
>> **What else should you know about your privacy?**
>> 
>> **If you choose to use the TutoringHut.com website you should be aware that any information transmitted electronically via the World Wide Web might not be secure. TutoringHut.com assumes no liability for the loss of any information that you transmit to us via the World Wide Web.**
>> 
>> **We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of TutoringHut.com, our employees, our users, or others**
>> 
>> **Information collected during registration and subsequent visits, such as your full name and location, may be displayed to other TutoringHut.com users in your User Profile or via the social networking component(s) of the site. You may control what personal information is displayed in your User Profile by visiting the Privacy Settings section of your profile.**
>> 
>> **The email address that you submit during registration, as well as your name and user identification, may be searchable by other TutoringHut.com users, unless you choose to opt out of this feature.**
>> 
>> **You may receive notification e-mails from TutoringHut.com regarding system information, online applications and/or wall posts. If you do not wish to receive e-mails from us, please change the Email Preferences setting of your User Profile and/or submit an email request to[info@TutoringHut.com](mailto:info@TutoringHut.com). Please note that you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.**
>> 
>> **In communicating with you, we may send e-mail as unencrypted plain text because we are aware that most customers cannot easily process encrypted e-mail. This is done for your convenience, but with the security concern that, if misrouted or intercepted, it could be read more easily than encrypted e-mail.**
>> 
>> **The use of virtual classrooms may involve the use of your computer’s webcam and/or microphone. Before either is activated you will be prompted to confirm use of such peripherals and any and all data transmitted through these means will be treated the same as any other data processed through the TutoringHut.com website.**
>> 
>> **Effective date of this policy and future modification**
>> 
>> **This privacy policy is effective as of 4/12/2010. TutoringHut.com reserves the right to make changes, deletions, modifications, or provide supplements to this policy from time to time. Changes will apply to the information collected after the date of changes as well as to existing information held by us and will take effect immediately upon publication, unless otherwise stated in writing by TutoringHut.com. You agree that the express acceptance by you, or your continued use of the TutoringHut.com website after publication of changes, shall constitute your acceptance of the privacy policy.**
